<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Another Random Blog</title>
    <link>/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Another Random Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Citing in Rmarkdown using zotero</title>
      <link>/2017/07/07/citing-in-rmarkdown-using-zotero/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/07/07/citing-in-rmarkdown-using-zotero/</guid>
      <description>Motivations The advantage of using Rmarkdown as a replacement of Word, libreoffice or other editors is tremendous and perfect in my current workflow, in which R coding, visualization are recorded for reproducibility and presentation.
For reports, manuscripts written in the academic style, sufficient reference is important because we are scientist and that’s what we do! all arguements should be backed up by evidence. In order to make the citation process painless, I did the following process and works for me (for now).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Notes For R</title>
      <link>/2017/05/15/my-notes-for-r/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/05/15/my-notes-for-r/</guid>
      <description> Live Dangerously.
 Problem I ran into a strange problem today. From a deep buried memory I remember that R supports import from compressed gzip files.
So I compressed a tab file and tried to read it.
gzip ~/  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Terminology in testing models so confusing that I neet to write it down as a reminder</title>
      <link>/2017/05/12/terminology-in-testing/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/05/12/terminology-in-testing/</guid>
      <description>About I usually get confused about these ideas so I think it’s a good idea to get it clear &amp;amp; write it down.
Question So we have a test set S, with a number of P positives and N negatives.
And we have a prediction method which assigns every sample with a label p and n.
True positive is the predicted positive and it’s true!
To give an evaluation of this methods:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My first post</title>
      <link>/2017/04/27/my-first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/04/27/my-first-post/</guid>
      <description>I like this quote:
 I web, therefore I am Spiderman
 </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>